

Behulum Wude

Sr. Product Support Specialist

♦ Alexandria, VA, 22311, United States

■ behulummd2018@gmail.com

• 2027909098

website-ruffw.ondigitalocean.app/ in linkedin.com/in/behulum-wude

Skills

• Excellent interpersonal and communication skills

Prior customer-facing experience, effectively communicates with the project team, multiple areas & divisions.

- Zendesk and intercom
 Administration and ticketing skills
- Manual QA test
 Mobile app and implementations on websites platforms
- Skil on Java, MS SQL, GitHub, and • • HTML

 Problem Solving and Decision-Making Skills

Thinking analytically, diverse research and skills

• **Troubleshooting**• • • • • • Provided outstanding user-level software support

- User onboarding and work on
 Identity verification software's like
 (jumio, ID.me)
- Microsoft Office (Word, Excel,
 PowerPoint, and SharePoint)

Zendesk, Salesforce, Slack, and Zoom • • • • • Experience with CRM & Google App Suite

Professional Experience

Dutchie, Product Support Specialist

11/2021 – present Bend,OR, United States

- Answer incoming customer requests via email, phone, and chat.
- Ticketing, issuing, and communication using JIRA.
- Provide education including technical, product, and compliance-related support for LeafLogix end-users.
- Performs the setup and testing of more complex systems.
- Identify hardware and software solutions
- Manage multiple complex issues simultaneously
- Test and verify solutions to new problems
- Tests and troubleshoots assemblies and/or final systems.
- Identify areas of improvement and lift up contact trends with the leadership team.
- Participate in knowledge sharing and issue escalations and resolutions within LeafLogix Support and cross-functional teams.
- Determines test specifications, methods, and procedures from a statement of work.
- Complete rework on assemblies and systems prepare technical reports summarizing findings and recommending solutions to technical problems.

Envel, Product Support Specialist

10/2020 - 11/2021 Boston, MA, United States

- Experience in Finance, (FinTech) Accounting, or Information systems department in an analyst role that provides end-user support
- Answering customer calls and emails, directly responding to questions, handling issues, and providing guidance on services, inquiries, adverse events, or complaints
- Increased annual total customer self-service rate by 6.2%, deflecting an additional 1500 tickets
- Managed knowledge base of 110+ Help Center articles, updating and creating content for product releases
- Led technical training and office hours to promote product mastery on a support team of 9 agents
- Collaborated with engineering and product teams to identify and deploy fixes for product limitations and bugs
- Focus on service excellence to all customers in a clear, effective, courteous, and professional manner
- Maintain call record rate, average talk times, and a low error rate

ID.me, Product Support Specialist

- Analyzed product feedback reports from direct consumers to identify, escalate and
- Managed Taxonomy Hygiene: identify tags impacted by bugs, launches, or other changes for reporting purposes
- Reviewed 200+ community threads, identify any emerging trends with top user issues or feature requests, and deep dive into those issues and raised bugs
- Escalation Reviews Monitor all product bugs and provide input as needed (research product features to repro, give additional troubleshooting, attach relevant feedback reports, etc.)
- Filed 30+ daily bugs regarding potential issues
- Created and presented bi-weekly reports to Product Teams, and Vendor Operations to validate workflows
- Monitor Product Forum for new emerging issues reported after user-facing product launches, fixes, and changes. Investigate one-off product escalations as needed and recommend response
- Resolved and provided guidance to engineers for escalated technical issues
- Collaborated with Product Support Specialist team members to scrub outstanding bug reports

Trader joe's, Crew Member

- Implemented daily order system method for the dry produce section based on previous and forecast sales.
- Developed a new merchandising plan for the most suitable representation of the dry produce.
- Created weekly merchandise displays by identifying popular and new items that customers requested frequently

ethio telecom, IT Support Specialist

- Deliver support for reported problems with desktop computers, laptops, peripherals, mobile devices, and IP/ POTS telephones
- Proactively monitors trends to prevent enterprise-level issues
- Provides administration and support to telecom-based phone systems
- Supervises and conducts the installation and configuration of desktop/laptop computer hardware, software, peripherals, and mobile devices using standard procedures
- Work with and coordinates vendors to troubleshoot and resolve issues
- Maintains the inventory of equipment available for re-use as required
- Research evaluates and provides recommendations to management on software, hardware, and telephony related technology being considered for use by Company's
- Writes documentation and/or reviews documentation written by others that describe the installation and operating procedures

01/2020 - 10/2020 MeLean, VA, United States

12/2018 – 12/2019 Alexandria,VA, United States

01/2015 – 12/2018 Hawassa, Ethiopia

Action for youth and community change, *Project Assistant*

01/2014 - 12/2015 Hawassa, Ethiopia

Youth and community development nonprofit organization

- Maintained and monitored project plans, project schedules, budgets, and expenditures for community programs, summer events, and mid-year youth programs.
- Hired and supervised trainers who led programs related to music, theater, and gymnastics for more than 50 children per year.
- Documented and followed up on important actions prepared necessary presentation materials for meetings

Profile

I am a technology passionate individual currently working as a product support specialist, at a leading software company focused on giving a great POS experience to the users.

I love computers, solving user problems, and helping people. when I am not working, you will find me playing soccer, hiking, biking, painting, hanging out with family and friends, and trying out new outdoor activities.

Education

HAWASSA UNIVERSITY, Information Technology

2014

Hawassa, Ethiopia

Merit America, Professional Development and IT Program

2019

DC, United States